[{"name": "Logitech BRIO Ultra HD Pro", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 9, "price_usd": 163.34, "resolution": "4K, 1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 3.2 Gen 1 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS", "fov_angle": "82\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech C920 HD Pro", "rating": 3, "rating_count": 14, "price_usd": 74.98, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS, Android", "fov_angle": "78\u00b0"}, {"name": "Asus ROG EYE", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 1, "price_usd": 224.98, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": null}, {"name": "Logitech C922 Pro Stream HD", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 9, "price_usd": 78.0, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS, Android", "fov_angle": "78\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech C920s HD Pro", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 6, "price_usd": 68.0, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS, Android", "fov_angle": "78\u00b0"}, {"name": "Razer Kiyo", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 9, "price_usd": 82.71, "resolution": "1080p, 720p, 480p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows", "fov_angle": "81.6\u00b0"}, {"name": "Razer Kiyo Pro", "rating": 5, "rating_count": 1, "price_usd": 185.96, "resolution": "1080p, 720p, 480p", "connection": "USB 3.2 Gen 1 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows", "fov_angle": "103\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech C270", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 5, "price_usd": 26.99, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS, Android", "fov_angle": "60\u00b0"}, {"name": "Avermedia PW513", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 179.99, "resolution": "4K, 1080p", "connection": "USB 3.2 Gen 1 Type-C", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "94\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech StreamCam", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 2, "price_usd": 149.99, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 3.2 Gen 1 Type-C", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "78\u00b0"}, {"name": "Wansview 101JD", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 2, "price_usd": 18.41, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": null, "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, Android", "fov_angle": "90\u00b0"}, {"name": "Adesso Cybertrack H4", "rating": 5, "rating_count": 2, "price_usd": 35.97, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Manual", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "78\u00b0"}, {"name": "Adesso Cybertrack H2", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 19.0, "resolution": "480p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "62\u00b0"}, {"name": "Creative Labs Live! Cam Sync 1080p", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 39.99, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "77\u00b0"}, {"name": "Adesso Cybertrack H6", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 70.37, "resolution": "4K", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "80\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech StreamCam", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 2, "price_usd": 149.99, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 3.2 Gen 1 Type-C", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "78\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech C925e", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 79.69, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, Linux", "fov_angle": "78\u00b0"}, {"name": "Wansview 102JD", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 19.98, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": null, "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, Android", "fov_angle": "90\u00b0"}, {"name": "Avermedia Live Streamer CAM 313", "rating": 5, "rating_count": 1, "price_usd": 55.98, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": null}, {"name": "Asus Webcam C3", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 49.99, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": null, "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS", "fov_angle": null}, {"name": "aoni A31", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 29.76, "resolution": "1080p, 720p, 480p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, Linux, ChromeOS, Android", "fov_angle": "84\u00b0"}, {"name": "AUKEY PC-LM1", "rating": 3, "rating_count": 5, "price_usd": null, "resolution": "1080p, 720p, 480p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Manual", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, Android", "fov_angle": "55\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech C310", "rating": 5, "rating_count": 1, "price_usd": 34.99, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS, Android", "fov_angle": "60\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech StreamCam Plus", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 143.63, "resolution": "1080p, 720p, 480p", "connection": "USB 3.2 Gen 1 Type-C", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": null}, {"name": "Green Extreme T200", "rating": 3, "rating_count": 2, "price_usd": 24.99, "resolution": "1080p, 720p, 480p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, Android", "fov_angle": "65\u00b0"}, {"name": "Microsoft LifeCam HD-3000", "rating": 3, "rating_count": 1, "price_usd": 27.67, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": null}, {"name": "Logitech C615 Portable", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 4, "price_usd": 69.99, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS, Android", "fov_angle": "78\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech B525", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 4, "price_usd": 64.99, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "69\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech C930e", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 81.87, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS", "fov_angle": "90\u00b0"}, {"name": "Adesso Cybertrack H5", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 45.97, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "80\u00b0"}, {"name": "Green Extreme T1000", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 179.0, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "120\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech C910", "rating": 5, "rating_count": 1, "price_usd": 149.99, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "78\u00b0"}, {"name": "Avermedia 4K UHD Webcam 510", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": null, "resolution": "4K, 1080p, 720p, 480p", "connection": "USB 3.2 Gen 1 Type-C", "focus_type": null, "operating_system": "Windows", "fov_angle": "85\u00b0"}, {"name": "Microsoft LifeCam Studio", "rating": 5, "rating_count": 1, "price_usd": 56.29, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "75\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech C505", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 49.99, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS", "fov_angle": "60\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech C525", "rating": 4, "rating_count": 2, "price_usd": 59.99, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS, Android", "fov_angle": "69\u00b0"}, {"name": "Adesso CyberTrack H3", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 28.97, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Manual", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": null}, {"name": "Avermedia PW315", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 119.99, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS", "fov_angle": "95.8\u00b0"}, {"name": "Green Extreme T300", "rating": 3, "rating_count": 1, "price_usd": 46.22, "resolution": "1080p, 720p, 480p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, Android", "fov_angle": "94\u00b0"}, {"name": "Avermedia PW310P", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 60.98, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS", "fov_angle": "73\u00b0"}, {"name": "Microsoft LifeCam Studio for Business", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 59.3, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "75\u00b0"}, {"name": "Logitech C505e", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 54.99, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, ChromeOS", "fov_angle": "60\u00b0"}, {"name": "VDO360 2SEE", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 99.99, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": null, "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, Linux, Android", "fov_angle": "75\u00b0"}, {"name": "Microsoft LifeCam CinemaaFor Business", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 42.77, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": null}, {"name": "Green Extreme T200 + Live Streaming Bundle", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": null, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, Android", "fov_angle": null}, {"name": "Microsoft Lifecam Cinema", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 43.29, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows", "fov_angle": "73\u00b0"}, {"name": "Microsoft LifeCam HD-3000 L2", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": 39.95, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": null}, {"name": "Creative Labs BlasterX Senz3D", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": null, "resolution": "1080p, 720p", "connection": "USB 3.2 Gen 1 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows", "fov_angle": "77\u00b0"}, {"name": "Creative Labs Live! Cam Sync HD", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": null, "resolution": "720p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Fixed", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": null}, {"name": "Adesso Cybertrack H4P", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": null, "resolution": "1080p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Manual", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X", "fov_angle": "78\u00b0"}, {"name": "Avermedia HD Webcam 310", "rating": 0, "rating_count": 0, "price_usd": null, "resolution": "1080p, 720p, 480p", "connection": "USB 2.0 Type-A", "focus_type": "Auto", "operating_system": "Windows, OS X, Android", "fov_angle": null}]